# Mukhammadzhon Khakimov

## Frontend Developer

Last update: November 27, 2022

Up-to-date version of CV is available at

https://Muhammadzhon.github.io/muhammad-bio

Residence	♠ Osh, Kyrgyzstan
Linkedin	in <u>Mukhammadzhon</u>
GitHub	Muhammadzhon
Phone	+996 (555) 00 43 45
Email	<u> hmuhammadjon</u>

English Russian Turkish HTML CSS JavaScript React SPA Github

I'm a self study frontend developer. The purpose for my last 5 years search happens to find the job which I love. And I realized only web developing going to fill my life path! After HTML CSS and JS learning React makes me confident and ambitions.

# **Professional Experience**

02/2021 - 10/2022

#### Dispatcher

Bilato holding takes leading position on delivering freight over USA and services 24/7 over 200 trucks and truck dri

As a dispatcher I'm responsible for:

- \* Scheduling truck drivers time and route
- st Monitoring pick-up, transit and drop off process of the loads
- \* Solving unexpected issues
- \* Quick response for drivers requests

Fluent English	Russian	Turkish	Communication		Customer service		Team work
----------------	---------	---------	---------------	--	------------------	--	-----------

03/2017 - 01/2021

### Sales Manager

Mukum Auto has history in auto market over 20 years

Responsibilities:

- \* Searching cars for purchase
- \* Diognosing and repairing
- \* Preparing for Sales
- st Dealing with potential buyers face to face and over phone



### Education

International Kazak-Turkish Ahmet Yesevi University [2011 - 2016]